Finding Aid to the Jacob M. Ulmer Papers, 1949-1969
History of Medicine Division, National Library of Medicine.
- Bound Volumes, 1948-1970
  - House Committee on Appropriation. Subcommittee Hearings on Appropriations for the Labor Department and Federal Security Agency, 1954-1955 (Box v.26-29)
  - House Committee on Appropriations. Subcommittee Hearings on Appropriations for the Departments of Labor and Health, Education, and Welfare, 1957-1968 (Box v.30-62)